= kisskh.lv =
Cha Dohyun!
Why did you leave without telling me?
Worried I'll try to
borrow your uniform again?
I'm dressed properly today.
Hey, are you sick?
Did you catch a cold in the rain yesterd—
Don't touch me.
What's with him?
[Sung Inho]
[Kim Domin]
[Summertime]
What the heck?
Good morning.
-Good morning.
Hello.
Where's the energy, boys?
Alright.
We have a new transfer student.
Quiet. Quiet down.
He's transferring in his
third year of high school,
a really hectic time.
It's very overwhelming for him.
Help him whenever you can,
so he can get settled in quickly.
Got it?
Yes.
Good.
[Cha Dohyun]
You always do whatever you want.
[OMG. So cute.]
[Cha Dohyun: It kept meowing in front
of my house in the middle of the night.]
[Don't think I can keep it. I'll get it
treated and put up for adoption.]
He looks so creepy.
It's exhausting just looking at him.
He looks so needy.
Again?
Yihyun, you can sit over there.
Okay.
Go on.
[Cha Dohyun: I'll get it treated
and put up for adoption.]
[I looked it up. It might be pink eye.]
[I'll go with you
to the vet after school!]
Eunho's so lucky.
What are you looking at? Look ahead!
Yes!
The college entrance exam is coming up.
Don't slack off, got it?
Yes.
Alright. Get ready for class.
See you later.
Hey.
Hey!
You're new here. You should
go around greeting your classmates.
You're a third year,
so it must be a forced transfer.
Definitely.
Hey! Hello?
Do you hear me?
Hello?
Maybe he's deaf.
Hey! Hey!
Shut up and get lost.
So arrogant.
I knew it from his weird eyes.
Your eyes...
Friend,
stop staring at me. It's annoying.
Who do you think you are?
His hair's cute.
What a nicely-shaped head.
OMG, you flinched!
Look at his face. I know he got scared!
Dude, you're so soft.
Are you dumb?
I'm just showing you some concern.
Why are you so sensitive, you loser—
I'm just here to graduate.
Please cooperate.
What the hell...
He asked us to cooperate.
Why do I have to cooperate?
What are you glaring at?
Smile.
Smile, you idiot!
Why are you so serious—
Hey, stop it.
What?
That's enough.
Are you the only ones in this classroom?
You're so noisy.
Bloody hell.
You saw everything.
He was the one who was being a rude prick.
Who's the rude prick here?
You were hitting him
and sexually harassing him.
Are you really surprised he was hostile?
Huh?
Oh, I see.
Did he go down on you?
Why are you so defensive of him?
It's better than you going down on me.
Go look in a mirror.
What the hell?
Stop! Stop!
Eunho! Stop...
That bastard!
Calm down.
Screw this.
Thanks.
If you want to thank me,
buy me something to eat.
You're not going to have lunch?
Yeah, the food today isn't good.
Don't you have to eat with them?
You don't have to worry about me.
Anyway, thank you.
What was your name again?
Kwon Yihyun.
Yihyun.
Are you rich?
Why did you transfer?
You don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
I'm gay.
I see.
After some classmates found out,
the bullying got severe.
Things got really out of hand.
The school strongly implied
that I transfer.
What a horrible school.
I said I like guys.
It must've been tough.
Are you okay with that?
Hey.
It's none of my business
that you like guys.
Is my opinion important?
Do you like me?
Right, what you think doesn't matter.
It's just that people
don't usually react like that.
You can have this.
Why are you eating snacks
instead of lunch?
Are you my mom?
Have you eaten?
Why didn't you text me back?
I was busy
preparing for the student council forum.
Council president work won't feed you.
Don't break your back over it.
Can I give it to him?
Yeah.
He paid for it.
I looked it up.
The cat probably has pink eye.
All it needs is eye drops.
If you're busy,
I'll go by myself.
It'll be over at eight.
I'll call you. Let's...
I'll go with you.
I had a pet cat.
You'll need help.
Really? Perfect.
Let's go together after school.
I haven't seen you before.
He's a new transfer student.
Say hi.
He's my friend, Cha Dohyun.
You are...
Kwon Yihyun.
Hello.
Transferring midway
through your third year
can only mean one thing.
Yeo Eunho,
you should know
how to pick the right friends by now.
Sheesh, where did that come from?
If I'm being picky,
I have to cut ties with you first.
Are you two close?
Yup.
He has a nasty temper,
so I'm his only friend.
You're the one with the nasty temper
without any other friends.
We're childhood friends by circumstance.
I see.
Childhood friends by circumstance, huh?
What are you doing?
Don't you need my gym uniform?
When did I say that?
It's PE class next.
Yihyun, see you later.
What's your problem? I can't breathe!
Call me like that too.
What?
Call me Dohyun.
Did you wake up
on the wrong side of the bed?
Dohyun. Dohyun!
Wait.
What are you doing?
What's wrong? It's not like
you've never seen me change.
See you.
[Yeo Eunho]
This short story was
originally titled "Girl."
Why did the writer change the title?
Let's find out.
"Rain Shower."
Short and impactful.
It's a sudden downpour
that leaves you no time to hide,
but it's over before you know it.
But after getting soaked,
your body becomes wet and sticky.
It's hard to dry off.
It leaves its trace.
Stop it!
[Yeo Eunho]
Like the girl's sweater stained
purple by grass.
[Yeo Eunho]
It was too heavy to be mere discomfort,
and too viscerally sticky
to be called jealousy.
[Yeo Eunho: I almost forgot.
Give me back my uniform.]
[Yeo Eunho: Check this out.]
Where are you?
Home, duh.
Just the two of you?
Yeah.
By the way, we went to the vet, and...
You sure you can take it home with you?
Yeah.
My oldest sister's been depressed
since our cat passed.
She's a freelancer and home all day.
It's better for it
to stay at my place than yours.
At least eat before you go.
I'm good.
Hey, why are you here?
I'm off. See you tomorrow.
Okay. Be safe.
Cha Dohyun!
Where are you going?
Aren't you here to see me?
There's something I have to do.
All of a sudden?
Yeah.
Hey. Hey! Leaving just like that?
Leave him alone.
Is this your cat?
I thought it didn't belong to anyone.
Answer me. Is it yours?
Shut up.
You like Yeo Eunho, don't you?
If not,
can I like him?
Do you really not know,
or are you pretending?
Hey!
Back off.
He
is mine.
[Summertime]
Let's go for tteokbokki after school.
Where are you going?
Get out of my way!
Let go!
I figured if I hung around you
long enough,
you'd eventually be mine.
But now it feels like
you're slipping through my fingers.
Cha Dohyun...
you've been acting strange.
Eunho.
Just believe what you see.
Cha Dohyun, you're not alone.
I'll be with you till the day I die.
You're the only one I have.